ACHYUT GHOSH

Buroshibtala, Chinsurah, West Bengal / achyutghosh06@gamil.com / +919804757023

Summary

Passionate programmer with 2.5+ years of experience working for an ERP software in the retail domain. My greatest strength is that I can quickly learn and master new technologies with proven success working in both a team and independently.

Skills

- C#
- EF Core
- Javascript
- API
- CSS

- .NET
- ORM
- SQL
- HTML
- Bootstrap

Experience

Ginni System Ltd. (Ginesys)

Software Developer, Kolkata, West Bengal 04/2021 - Present

- **Ginesys Webhook:** Developed an event-driven webhook application to notify the changes in ERP modules.
 - Tech Stack: C#, .Net Core, Oracle DB, RESTful API, Webhook
- **Event Data Service:** Devised a solution to provide a gateway to send data from the ERP modules synchronized between Ginesys and other applications.
 - Tech Stack: C#, .Net Core, LINQ, Oracle DB, RESTful API
- Migration of Finance Module: Migrated the existing RESTful APIs from ADO .NET to EF Core 3.1.
 - Tech Stack: C#, .NET Core, ORM, Oracle, DDD

Ginni System Ltd. (Ginesys)

Junior Software Developer, Kolkata, West Bengal 08/2019 - 03/2021

- **Plugin Sync:** Developed a sync mechanism from POS to HO to share different plugin DLLs & config files (e.g. Paytm Integration).
 - Tech Stack: C#, .NET Framework, MS SQL, LINQ
- Omni-Channel Notifiers: These notifiers act as middleware between GDS and the aggregators. It is responsible to orchestrate the data flow in the GDS queue to the destination.
 - Tech Stack: C#, .Net Core, SQLite, LINQ, Dapper, Oracle DB, MS SQL, RESTful API
- **UI Development:** Developed some UI forms using the JavaScript framework for the Admin module in the Ginesys ERP.
 - Tech Stack: JavaScript, Sencha, MVVM

Ginni System Ltd. (Ginesys)

Software Developer Intern, Kolkata, West Bengal 04/2019 - 07/2019

- WMS API: Responsible to develop RESTFull APIs for the WMS module in .NET Framework.
 - Tech Stack: C#, .NET Framework, Oracle, ORM

Education

MCA

University of Calcutta, Kolkata, West Bengal 06/2019

Graduated with distinction marks (71%)

B.Sc. in Mathematics

University of Burdwan, Chandannagar, West Bengal 05/2016

Graduated with first class marks (60.25%)

High Secondary (12th)

WBCHSE, Chandannagar, West Bengal 05/2013

Completed with 66.25% marks

Secondary (10th)

WBBSE, Chandannagar, West Bengal 06/2011

Completed with 80.25% marks

Accomplishment

Stock Market Prediction Using LSTM On Indian Share Market: This project was published at 32nd International Conference on Computer Applications in Industry and Engineering 2019, in the EPiC Series in Computing, volume 63, pages 101-110.

Link: https://easychair.org/publications/paper/LKgn

Languages

- English
- Bengali

Hindi

Hobby

- · Reading several types of non-fiction books
- · Playing and learning Ukulele